[{"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small round in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black, one small round in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one large square in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small square in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small round in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one large square in black, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one small round in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in black, one small square in black, one small square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large round in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large round in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black, one small round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one small round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in black, one small round in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small round in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one small round in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in black, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one large round in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small round in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large square in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one large round in black, one middle round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in black, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one small square in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in black, one small round in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black, one small round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one large round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in black, one small round in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in black, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in black, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in black, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in black, one small square in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in black, one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in black, one small round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one large square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one small square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in black, one small round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large square in black, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large square in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in black, one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one small round in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small square in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one small round in blue, one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle square in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in yellow, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large round in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in blue, one large round in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small square in black, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one large round in blue, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small square in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in blue, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in blue, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in black, one small triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one large round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one large round in black, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one small square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one large round in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one small square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small square in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large round in blue, one middle square in black, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in black, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in black, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one middle triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large round in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one large square in black, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in black, one middle round in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "small", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in blue, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one small round in blue, one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one small square in yellow, one small round in black, one small square in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in blue, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one middle square in yellow, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small square in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "square", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in black, one small round in black, one middle square in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue, one small square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in black, one middle round in black. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in black, one large square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one small square in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow, one small square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in black, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small square in yellow, one small square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue, one small square in black, one small round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in black, one small triangle in blue, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one middle square in blue, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in blue, one large square in black, one small round in black. In the middle box, there are one large square in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in blue, one small square in yellow, one large round in black, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "small", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one large round in blue, one large round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one small square in black, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the left box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue, one small square in black, one small square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle round in blue. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["yellow", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["black", "round", "middle", "middle"], ["blue", "round", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in black, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in yellow, one large square in black, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one middle triangle in black, one large triangle in blue, one small round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["black", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["blue", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in black, one small round in blue. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one large square in black, one middle round in blue, one small round in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in black, one small square in black, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one middle square in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small square in blue, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one large round in blue. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in black, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large round in black, one small round in blue, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large round in yellow, one large round in blue, one large round in black, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one middle triangle in black, one large square in yellow, one large square in black, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the right box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["blue", "round", "large", "middle"], ["blue", "square", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle round in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one large triangle in black, one large round in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in blue, one large square in yellow, one large triangle in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one small square in yellow, one large round in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in blue, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black, one small square in black, one large round in blue, one middle round in blue.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large triangle in blue, one middle round in blue, one middle square in black. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle square in black, one large square in black. In the middle box, there are one small round in blue, one small square in black, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in blue, one large square in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": []}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small square in black, one large square in black, one large round in blue, one large triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue. In the right box, there are one large round in black, one small square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "left"], ["black", "square", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one large square in black, one small square in blue. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one large round in blue, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in black, one small square in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the left box", "answer": [["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"], ["black", "square", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in black, one large square in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large triangle in blue.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["black", "square", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle triangle in black, one small round in yellow, one small square in black, one small round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in yellow, one small triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in black, one middle square in black, one large triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in blue, one small round in black, one large triangle in blue, one small triangle in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one middle square in black, one large square in blue, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "middle"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one large round in blue, one large square in black, one small square in black, one middle square in yellow, one large round in black. In the right box, there are one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "small", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small square in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle square in blue, one large square in blue, one middle square in blue, one large triangle in yellow, one small round in blue, one large square in black.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the middle box", "answer": [["black", "triangle", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small square in blue, one middle triangle in blue. In the middle box, there are one large square in black, one large round in black, one large triangle in blue, one large triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one large square in blue, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow, one small triangle in black.", "question": "How to move all yellow objects to the right box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "middle", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "left"], ["yellow", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle round in black, one small round in black, one middle square in yellow. In the right box, there are one small round in blue, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle square in blue, one small round in yellow, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["blue", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "small", "right"], ["black", "round", "middle", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one middle square in black, one middle triangle in blue, one middle round in black, one middle square in blue, one small triangle in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large round in blue, one large square in yellow, one small round in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one middle round in yellow, one large round in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large round in blue.", "question": "How to move all triangles to the left box", "answer": [["yellow", "triangle", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "triangle", "small", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in yellow, one middle square in black, one small round in blue, one small round in blue, one small triangle in black, one large round in black. In the middle box, there are one middle square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow, one large triangle in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one small triangle in yellow, one middle triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all black objects to the right box", "answer": [["black", "square", "middle", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "small", "left"], ["black", "round", "large", "left"], ["black", "triangle", "large", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one small round in black, one middle triangle in black. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one middle round in blue, one large square in blue, one middle triangle in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in black, one small triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in black, one large round in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the left box", "answer": [["black", "round", "middle", "right"], ["yellow", "round", "large", "right"], ["blue", "round", "middle", "middle"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large triangle in black, one small square in blue, one small round in yellow, one large triangle in black, one middle triangle in yellow, one middle square in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one large triangle in black, one small triangle in black, one middle round in yellow. In the right box, there are one large square in blue, one small triangle in blue, one small round in yellow, one large square in yellow, one small round in blue, one middle round in black.", "question": "How to move all squares to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "square", "small", "left"], ["yellow", "square", "middle", "left"], ["blue", "square", "large", "right"], ["yellow", "square", "large", "right"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large round in black, one middle round in blue, one small triangle in yellow, one middle round in yellow. In the middle box, there are one small square in yellow, one small round in yellow, one small round in blue, one small triangle in blue. In the right box, there are one small triangle in yellow, one large square in yellow.", "question": "How to move all blue objects to the middle box", "answer": [["blue", "round", "middle", "left"]]}, {"story": "There are three boxes. In the left box, there are one large square in black, one small square in black, one large round in yellow, one middle square in blue. In the middle box, there are one large round in yellow, one large square in black. In the right box, there are one middle triangle in yellow, one small square in yellow, one large triangle in yellow.", "question": "How to move all rounds to the middle box", "answer": [["yellow", "round", "large", "left"]]}]